[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the movie Die Hard come out?", "correct_answer": "1988", "incorrect_answers": ["1984", "1982", "1990"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Emma Thompson won an Academy Award for the Sense and Sensibility screenplay based on the novel of the same name by this famous English writer.", "correct_answer": "Jane Austen", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlotte Bronte", "Emily Bronte", "George Eliot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is Westley, AKA Dread Pirate Roberts, kept prisoner in the movie The Princess Bride?", "correct_answer": "The Pit of Despair", "incorrect_answers": ["The Pit of Insanity", "The Pit of Dread", "The Pit of Torture"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The bustard is a frog.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred alongside Sandra Bullock as her partner and love interest in the 2000 comedy movie Miss Congeniality?", "correct_answer": "Benjamin Bratt", "incorrect_answers": ["Keanu Reeves", "Ben Afleck", "Vince Vaughn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Debra Winger starred in the 1993 Australian movie The Piano and played most of the piano sequences herself.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She played Bea Arthurs mother on Golden Girls.", "correct_answer": "Estelle Getty", "incorrect_answers": ["Betty White", "Ellen Corby", "Dorothy Zbornak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river is considered the longest river on the planet?", "correct_answer": "The Nile", "incorrect_answers": ["The Tigris", "The Mississippi", "The Amazon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of domino game is Bergen?", "correct_answer": "Scoring domino game", "incorrect_answers": ["Both blocking and scoring domino game", "Blocking domino game", "Neither blocking nor scoring domino game"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest mall in the world, as of 2007.", "correct_answer": "The South China Mall", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bejing Mall", "The West Edmonton Mall", "The Raja Mall at Mombai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "New York City is divided into 5 boroughs. One of these is not part of NYC?", "correct_answer": "Yonkers", "incorrect_answers": ["Richmond", "The Bronx", "Staten Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Manfred Albrecht Freiherr von Richthofen was a German pilot and is still regarded today as the ace of aces. Which of the following pairs (nickname - nation calling him that) is wrong?", "correct_answer": "They are all true.", "incorrect_answers": ["Red Battle-Flyer - the Germans", "Red Devil - the French", "Red Baron - the British"]}]